Capital Defender Office; Records apap309
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Capital Defender Office Records1975-2007
1995-2007
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Capital Defender Office (N.Y.)
apap309
116.73 cubic ft.
The Capital Defender Office (1995-2008) (CDO) was established as part of New York States 1995 death penalty legislation which took effect on September 1, 1995. Under the new law, the State expanded the crime of first degree murder and introduced two new penalties, death and life in prison without possibility of parole, for those convicted. Working from offices in Albany, New York City, and Rochester, the CDO sought to ensure that defendants being tried by the State, who could not afford representation, receive skilled counsel in capital cases. The CDO closed its Rochester office in 2005, and, as no state death penalty cases remain, the Albany and New York City offices in 2008. This collection consists of news clips (filed by subject), subject files, bound records of appeal in the cases of the People v. Cahill, Harris, LaValle, Mateo, McCoy, and Taylor, notebooks with appellate briefs, New York county court papers arranged by county, government studies, reports and debates on capital punishment, annual reports, and a small number of VHS tapes recording court proceedings. There are defendant case files, some with correspondence, court papers, and news clips and others with just news clips.
Administrative History
Capital punishment was returned to the criminal statutes of New York State by Chapter 1 of the Laws of 1995, which took effect on September 1, 1995. The new law expanded the crime of first degree murder, and provided two new penalties for persons convicted of first degree murder: death and life in prison without the possibility of parole.
The Capital Defender Office [CDO] was established under New York State's death penalty statute and was given the statutory mandate of ensuring that defendants who cannot afford adequate representation in capital cases receive effective assistance of counsel. The statute also charged the CDO with creating an effective system of capital defense throughout New York State. This system of capital defense is ensured through several means, including: Providing direct representation of capital defendants; Helping to identify private attorneys to represent capital defendants; Entering agreements with legal aid societies and other defender organizations to accept appointments in capital cases; Monitoring the performance and accounting of such defender organizations; Providing private attorneys with continuing legal advice and other assistance; Promulgating standards that attorneys must meet to qualify to defend capital cases; Providing or arranging for representation in capital cases before permanent appointment of counsel; Providing the criminal defense bar with training and continuing legal education about death penalty practice and law.
Since the office was established, 10,000 murders have occurred in New York. Prosecutors considered bringing the death penalty in 877 capital-eligible cases, and district attorneys filed notice of intent to seek the death penalty in 58 cases. Juries in only seven cases ultimately returned death sentences. No one was executed.
Kevin Doyle, executive director and the first Capital Defender in New Yorks history, preceded over the capital cases in New York during the period. Doyle had practiced in New York both in a big firm and in the public defenders office, and had also tried capital cases in Alabama. A three-person board of directors, which met on a regular basis to review office policy, governed the CDO. The Capital Defender, appointed by the Board of Directors, ran the agency and was responsible for building the state's capital defense system. In 1995, the CDO established three offices to provide capital representation, one in Albany, one in Rochester, and one in New York City. The Rochester office was closed on October 31, 2005, and the other two on June 13, 2008.
Scope and Contents
The New York State Capital Defender Office Records represent the work of New York State capital defenders during reinstatement (following Furman v. Georgia) of the death penalty in New York from the period of 1995- 2007.The records showcase the capital cases that members of the CDO defended against.
The Capital Defender Office collection consists of news clips (filed by date), subject files, bound records of appeal in the cases of the People v. Cahill, Harris, LaValle, Mateo, McCoy, and Taylor, notebooks with appellate briefs, New York county court papers arranged by county of Murder Two indictments, government studies, reports and debates on capital punishment, annual reports, and a small number of VHS tapes recording court proceedings.
Series one, the appellate briefs were separated upon donation on the material. The archivist choose to keep these briefs as the CDO did and did not integrate the appellate briefs with the bound records on appeal cases.
Much of the collection is a vast collection of news clipping documenting the death penalty in New York State. The news clippings are organized by year but there has been minimal processing to the news clippings. The donor has a set of original clips as well as duplicates of the same materials. The processing team choose to not to move the materials for the original order because the materials have been arranged by year and could be given back to the donor. The materials are kept onsite.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is organized into the following series:
Series 1: Appellate Briefs
Series 2: Capital Defender Case Files
Subseries 1:Mateo Record
Subseries 2: LaValle Record
Subseries 3: McCoy Record
Subseries 4: Taylor Record
Subseries 5: Harris Record
Subseries 6: Cahill Record
Series 3: Death Row Conditions
Series 4: Murder Two Indictments
Series 5: Subject Files
Series 6: Clippings
Acquisition Information
The Capital Defender Office of New York transferred their records to the M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives in 2008.
Access
Access to this record group is unrestricted.
Death Penalty; Capital punishment--Moral and ethical aspects; Capital punishment--United States; Death Penalty; Abolition movement--United States; Administrative reports; Clippings; Legal documents; Criminal court records; Doyle, Kevin M.; Capital Defender Office (N.Y.)
- Appellate Briefs, 2000-2007; 1; 6.3 cubic ft.
  Arrangement
  Arranged Alphabetically.
  Scope and Contents
  The appellate brief series is compiled of the appellate brief transcripts filed with the State of New York Court of Appeals from the seven cases that the Capital Defender Office represented on. The materials are arranged alphabetically by defendants last name.
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. James F. Cahill, 2002 May 24 (Box 1 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 1)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. James F. Cahill, 2003 May 24 (Box 1 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 2)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. James F. Cahill, 2004 May 24 (Box 1 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 3)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. James F. Cahill, 2005 May 24 (Box 1 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 4)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. James F. Cahill (1 of 2), 2006 May 24 (Box 1 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 5)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. James F. Cahill (2 of 2), 2007 May 24 (Box 1 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 6)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. James F. Cahill (1 of 3), 2003 April 15 (Box 1 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 7)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. James F. Cahill (2 of 3), 2004 April 15 (Box 1 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 8)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. James F. Cahill (3 of 3), 2005 April 15 (Box 1 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 9)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. James F. Cahill, 2003 July 21 (Box 1 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 10)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. James F. Cahill, 2004 July 21 (Box 1 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 11)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. Darrell K. Harris, 2000 October 17 (Box 1 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 12)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. Darrell K. Harris, 2000 October 17 (Box 2 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 1)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. Darrell K. Harris, 2000 October 17 (Box 2 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 2)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. Darrell K. Harris, 2000 October 17 (Box 2 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 3)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. Darrell K. Harris (1 of 2), 2000 October 17 (Box 2 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 4)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. Darrell K. Harris (2 of 2), 2000 October 17 (Box 2 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 5)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. Darrell K. Harris (1 of 3), 2001 October 25 (Box 2 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 6)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. Darrell K. Harris (2 of 3), 2001 October 25 (Box 2 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 7)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. Darrell K. Harris (3 of3), 2001 October 25 (Box 2 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 8)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. Darrell K. Harris, 2002 April 2 (Box 2 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 9)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. Darrell K. Harris (1 of 2), 2002 April 2 (Box 2 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 10)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. Darrell K. Harris (2 of 2), 2002 April 2 (Box 2 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 11)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. Stephen S. LaValle, 2002 December 20 (Box 2 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 12)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. Stephen S. LaValle, 2002 December 20 (Box 2 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 13)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. Stephen S. LaValle, 2002 December 20 (Box 2 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 14)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. Stephen S. LaValle, 2002 December 20 (Box 3 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 1)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. Stephen S. LaValle, 2002 December 20 (Box 3 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 2)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. Stephen S. LaValle (1 of 2), 2002 December 20 (Box 3 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 3)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. Stephen S. LaValle (2 of 2), 2002 December 20 (Box 3 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 4)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. Stephen S. LaValle, 2003 December 11 (Box 3 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 5)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. Angel L. Mateo, 2003 January 24 (Box 3 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 6)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. Angel L. Mateo, 2003 January 24 (Box 3 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 7)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. Angel L. Mateo, 2003 January 24 (Box 3 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 8)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. Angel L. Mateo, 2003 January 24 (Box 3 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 9)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. Angel L. Mateo, 2003 January 24 (Box 3 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 10)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. Angel L. Mateo, 2003 January 24 (Box 3 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 11)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. Angel L. Mateo, 2003 January 24 (Box 3 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 12)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. Angel L. Mateo, 2003 January 24 (Box 3 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 13)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. Angel L. Mateo, 2003 September 3 (Box 3 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 14)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. Nicholson McCoy, 2004 January 16 (Box 4 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 1)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. Nicholson McCoy, 2004 January 16 (Box 4 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 2)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. Nicholson McCoy, 2004 January 16 (Box 4 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 3)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. Nicholson McCoy, 2004 January 16 (Box 4 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 4)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. Nicholson McCoy (1 of 2), 2004 January 16 (Box 4 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 5)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. Nicholson McCoy (2 of 2), 2004 January 16 (Box 4 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 6)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. Nicholson McCoy, Undated (Box 4 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 7)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. Nicholson McCoy, Undated (Box 4 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 8)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. Nicholson McCoy, Undated (Box 4 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 9)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. Nicholson McCoy, Undated (Box 4 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 10)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. Nicholson McCoy, Undated (Box 5 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 1)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. Nicholson McCoy, Undated (Box 5 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 2)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. Nicholson McCoy, Undated (Box 5 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 3)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. Nicholson McCoy, Undated (Box 5 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 4)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. Nicholson McCoy, Undated (Box 5 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 5)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. Nicholson McCoy, Undated (Box 5 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 6)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. Nicholson McCoy, Undated (Box 5 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 7)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. Robert Yale Shulman (1 of 2), 2004 March 25 (Box 5 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 8)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. Robert Yale Shulman (1 of 2), 2004 March 25 (Box 6 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 1)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. John Taylor, 2006 August 31 (Box 6 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 2)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. John Taylor, 2006 August 31 (Box 6 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 3)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. John Taylor, 2006 August 31 (Box 6 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 4)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. John Taylor, 2006 August 31 (Box 6 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 5)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. John Taylor, 2006 August 31 (Box 6 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 6)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. John Taylor, 2007 April 2 (Box 6 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 7)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. John Taylor, 2007 April 2 (Box 6 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 8)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. John Taylor, 2007 April 2 (Box 6 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 9)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. John Taylor, 2007 July 19 (Box 6 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 10)
  - Apellate Brief - The People of the State of New York vs. John Taylor, 2007 July 19 (Box 7 (1-Appellate Briefs), Folder 1)
- Capital Defender Case Files, 1996-2003; 2; 33.63 cubic ft.
  Arranged Chronologically by Volume.
  The Capital Defender Case Files are the volumes of record on appeal for six cases that the Captal Defender Officer defended against. The six cases included are the People v. Mateo, LaValle, McCoy, Taylor, Harris, and Cahill.
  - Mateo Record, 1996-1998; 2.1; 5.88 cubic ft.
    Arranged by Chronologically by Volume.
    The record on appeal for Mateo v. State of New York, volumes 1-36.
    - Mateo v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 1, 1996 October 11 - 1999 April 13 (Oversized 1)
    - Mateo v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 2, 1997 April 24 (Oversized 1)
    - Mateo v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 3, 1997 April 24 (Oversized 1)
    - Mateo v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 4, 1997 April 24 (Oversized 1)
    - Mateo v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 5, 1997 April 24 (Oversized 2)
    - Mateo v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 6, 1997 April 24 - June 12 (Oversized 2)
    - Mateo v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 7, 1997 June 12 - June 24 (Oversized 2)
    - Mateo v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 8, 1997 June 24 - 1998 February 24 (Oversized 2)
    - Mateo v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 9, 1998 February 24 - September 15 (Oversized 3)
    - Mateo v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 10, 1998 September 16 - December 4 (Oversized 3)
    - Mateo v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 11, 1998 December 4 - 1999 March 8 (Oversized 3)
    - Mateo v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 12, 1997 April 24 - 1998 November 12 (Oversized 3)
    - Mateo v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 13, 1997 June 19 - December 8 (Oversized 4)
    - Mateo v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 14, 1997 December 8 - 1998 February 5 (Oversized 4)
    - Mateo v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 15, 1997 December 31 - 1998 July 6 (Box 1 (2-Capital Defender Case Files), Folder 1)
    - Mateo v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 16, 1996 November 7 - 1997 July 2 (Oversized 4)
    - Mateo v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 17, 1997 July 28 - July 31 (Oversized 4)
    - Mateo v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 18, 1997 August 22 - 1998 August 20 (Oversized 5)
    - Mateo v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 19, 1998 September 24 - September 29 (Oversized 5)
    - Mateo v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 20, 1998 September 30 - October 5 (Oversized 5)
    - Mateo v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 21, 1998 October 6 - October 9 (Oversized 5)
    - Mateo v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 22, 1998 October 9 - October 20 (Oversized 6)
    - Mateo v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 23, 1998 October 21 - October 22 (Box 1 (2-Capital Defender Case Files), Folder 2)
    - Mateo v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 24, 1998 October 23 - October 27 (Oversized 6)
    - Mateo v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 25, 1998 October 28 - October 29 (Oversized 6)
    - Mateo v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 26, 1998 October 30 - November 9 (Oversized 6)
    - Mateo v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 27, 1998 November 5 - November 9 (Oversized 7)
    - Mateo v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 28, 1998 November 12 - November 13 (Box 1 (2-Capital Defender Case Files), Folder 3)
    - Mateo v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 29, 1998 November 16 - November 20 (Oversized 7)
    - Mateo v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 30, 1998 November 23 - November 25 (Oversized 7)
    - Mateo v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 31, 1998 November 30 - December 4 (Oversized 7)
    - Mateo v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 32, 1998 December 8 - 1999 January 15 (Oversized 8)
    - Mateo v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 33, 1998 December 15 (Oversized 8)
    - Mateo v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 34, 1996 December 12 - 2001 November 8 (Box 1 (2-Capital Defender Case Files), Folder 4)
    - Mateo v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 35, Undated (Oversized 8)
    - Mateo v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 36, Undated (Oversized 8)
  - LaValle Record, 1997-2003; 2.2; 5.88 cubic ft.
    The record on appeal for LaValle v. State of New York, volumes 1-33. This series also contains supplmental case material.
    - LaValle v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 1, 1997 June 3 - 1999 September 13 (Oversized 9)
    - LaValle v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 2, 1998 March 27 - 1999 July 30 (Oversized 9)
    - LaValle v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 3, 1998 October 3 - 1999 July 23 (Oversized 9)
    - LaValle v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 4, 1999 July 23 - 2000 January 7 (Oversized 9)
    - LaValle v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 5, 1997 June 19 - 1999 November 13 (Oversized 10)
    - LaValle v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 6, 1998 October 16 - 1999 May 28 (Oversized 10)
    - LaValle v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 7, 1997 June 3 - 1998 June 17 (Oversized 10)
    - LaValle v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 8, 1998 June 17 - 1999 February 1 (Oversized 10)
    - LaValle v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 9, 1999 March 8 - March 11 (Oversized 11)
    - LaValle v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 10, 1999 March 15 - March 18 (Oversized 11)
    - LaValle v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 11, 1999 March 22 - March 23 (Oversized 11)
    - LaValle v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 12, 1999 March 24 - March 25 (Oversized 11)
    - LaValle v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 13, 1999 March 29 - April 1 (Oversized 12)
    - LaValle v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 14, 1999 April 5 (Box 1 (2-Capital Defender Case Files), Folder 1)
    - LaValle v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 15, 1999 April 6 - April 8 (Oversized 12)
    - LaValle v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 16, 1999 April 8 - April 13 (Oversized 12)
    - LaValle v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 17, 1999 April 14 - April 20 (Oversized 12)
    - LaValle v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 18, 1999 April 21 - April 22 (Oversized 13)
    - LaValle v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 19, 1999 April 26 - April 28 (Oversized 13)
    - LaValle v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 20, 1999 April 29 - May 6 (Oversized 13)
    - LaValle v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 21, 1999 May 10 - May 12 (Oversized 13)
    - LaValle v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 22, 1999 May 13 - May 18 (Oversized 14)
    - LaValle v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 23, 1999 May 19 - May 24 (Oversized 14)
    - LaValle v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 24, 1999 June 2 - June 9 (Oversized 14)
    - LaValle v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 25, 1999 June 10 - June 15 (Oversized 14)
    - LaValle v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 26, 1999 June 16 - June 21 (Oversized 15)
    - LaValle v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 27, 1999 June 22 - June 24 (Oversized 15)
    - LaValle v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 28, 1999 June 28 - June 30 (Oversized 15)
    - LaValle v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 29, 1999 July 1 - July 12 (Oversized 15)
    - LaValle v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 30, 1999 July 14 - July 17 (Oversized 16)
    - LaValle v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 31, 1999 July 27 - December 17 (Oversized 16)
    - LaValle v. State of New York Record on Appeal Volume 33, 1997 June 9 - 2001 June 29 (Oversized 16)
    - LaValle v. State of New York Record on Appeal Supplement, 2003 July 22 (Box 1 (2-Capital Defender Case Files), Folder 1)
  - McCoy Record, 1998-2000; 2.3; 6.56 cubic ft.